{"data":[{"question":"The students suggested buying flowers for the teachers in the Teachers' Day.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The students","b":"buying","c":"for","d":"in","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- in-> on","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"No one have solved such a difficult problem.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"have","b":"solved","c":"such","d":"difficult","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Have-> has","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"During their meat, they discussed what to do at the weekend.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"During","b":"meat","c":"to do","d":"at","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Meat-> meal","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"If you write the essay careful, you will get good mark.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"If","b":"write","c":"careful","d":"will","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Careful-> carefully","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Ordinary Americans are friendly and not afraid to show its feelings.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Ordinary","b":"are","c":"not","d":"its","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Its-> their","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The girl who were injured in the accident is now in hospital.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"who","b":"were","c":"in","d":"is","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Were-> was","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Thank you very much of the present that you sent me.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"very","b":"much","c":"of","d":"that","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Of-> for","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"There wasn't some directory in the telephone box from which I was phoning.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"wasn't","b":"some","c":"the","d":"from","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Some-> any","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The man who I was waiting for didn't turn up.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The man","b":"who","c":"was","d":"for","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Who-> whom","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Women wear make-up to beautiful themselves.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"wear","b":"make-up","c":"beautiful","d":"themselves","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Beautiful-> beautify","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}